<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BNA</string>
    <!-- strings.xml -->
    <string name="maintaining">
Maintaining association amongst all dedicated to neurological sciences
</string>
    <!-- strings.xml -->
    <string name="aims_of_bna">
Aims of BNA
</string>
    <!-- strings.xml -->
    <string name="view_all">
 View All
</string>
    <!-- strings.xml -->
    <string name="month">
Case of the Month
</string>
    <string name="privacy">
        About Us
    </string>
    <!-- strings.xml -->
    <string name="dr_ketan_de">
Dr. Ketan Desai
</string>
    <!-- strings.xml -->
    <string name="committee">
Committee
</string>
    <string name="no_data_available">No data available</string>

    <!-- strings.xml -->
    <string name="president">
President\u000D
</string>
    <!-- strings.xml -->
    <string name="login_as_bn">
Login as BNA Member
</string>
    <!-- strings.xml -->
    <string name="this_month">
 All Notifications
</string>
    <!-- strings.xml -->
    <string name="login_as_bna">
Login as BNA Member
</string>
    <!-- strings.xml -->
    <string name="username">
Member number
</string>
    <!-- strings.xml -->
    <string name="email">
Email or phone number
</string>

    <string name="sh1">B9:69:37:D9:DF:23:64:6F:05:A3:E6:E1:87:FD:0D:F2:7E:F6:DE:62
</string>
    <string name="sh256">6F:62:A6:A1:43:56:34:CE:B6:26:9B:64:5D:EA:B8:8A:17:A7:95:83:AF:0A:FC:2B:60:1F:46:DD:C9:AB:D5:61</string>
    <string name="title_activity_notification2">Notification2Activity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <!-- res/values/strings.xml -->

 <!--   <string name="about_bna_app_content">
    <![CDATA[
    This App is meant for use by BNA members as well as delegates attending BNA meetings. The app offers many features to ensure connectivity of users with BNA as well as access to regular academic and learning content from BNA. App gives access to:<br/>
    <ul style="list-style-type: disc; padding-left: 30px;">
        <li style="font-size: 1.5em; margin-bottom: 10px;">Notification from BNA to update users about upcoming events, academic activities, journal issues, etc</li>
        <li style="font-size: 1.5em; margin-bottom: 10px;">Event details for quarterly &amp; annual meetings with detailed Scientific Program</li>
        <li style="font-size: 1.5em; margin-bottom: 10px;">Journal of BNA, published at regular intervals</li>
        <li style="font-size: 1.5em; margin-bottom: 10px;">Interesting Cases that help users to learn and also participate with comments</li>
        <li style="font-size: 1.5em; margin-bottom: 10px;">Participate and win prizes in Quiz during events, through the Voting section</li>
    </ul>
    For any technical queries regarding the app, please contact <a href="mailto:digitalheatlh@cmplin.com">digitalheatlh@cmplin.com</a>
]]>
</string>-->

<!--
    <string name="about_bna_app_content">
    <![CDATA[
    This App is meant for use by BNA members as well as delegates attending BNA meetings.<br/>
    The app offers many features... App gives access to:<br/>
    <span style="font-size: 5em;">•</span> Notification from BNA to update users...<br/>
    <span style="font-size: 2em;">•</span> Event details for quarterly &amp; annual meetings...<br/>
    <span style="font-size: 2em;">•</span> Journal of BNA, published at regular intervals<br/>
    <span style="font-size: 2em;">•</span> Interesting Cases that help users to learn and participate<br/>
    <span style="font-size: 2em;">•</span> Participate and win prizes in Quiz during events<br/>
    For any technical queries regarding the app, please contact
    <a href="mailto:digitalheatlh@cmplin.com">digitalheatlh@cmplin.com</a>
    ]]>
</string>-->


    <string name="about_bna_app_content"><!--This App is meant for use by BNA members as well as delegates attending BNA meetings.
        The app offers many features to ensure connectivity of users with BNA as well as access
        to regular academic and learning content from BNA. App gives access to:\n\n
        <span style="font-size:50px;"><b>•</b></span> Notification from BNA to update users about upcoming events, academic activities, journal issues, etc\n\n
        <span style="font-size:50px;"><b>• </b></span> Event details for quarterly &amp; annual meetings with detailed Scientific Program\n\n
        <span style="font-size:50px;"><b>• </b></span> Journal of BNA, published at regular intervals\n\n
        <span style="font-size:50px;"><b>• </b></span> Interesting Cases that help users to learn and also participate with comments\n\n
        <span style="font-size:50px;"><b>• </b></span> Participate and win prizes in Quiz during events, through the Voting section\n\n

      -->For any technical queries regarding the app, please contact <a href="mailto:digitalheatlh@cmplin.com">digitalheatlh@cmplin.com</a>
    </string>


<!--    <string name="about_bna_app_content">
    This App is meant for use by BNA members as well as delegates attending BNA meetings.
    The app offers many features to ensure connectivity of users with BNA as well as access
    to regular academic and learning content from BNA. App gives access to:\n
    <b>• </b>Notification from BNA to update users about upcoming events, academic activities, journal issues, etc
</string>-->

    <!--<string name="about_bna_app_content">This App is meant for use by BNA members as well as delegates attending BNA meetings. The app offers many features to ensure connectivity of users with BNA as well as access to regular academic and learning content from BNA. App gives access to:\n\n
        <b>•</b> Notification from BNA to update users about upcoming events, academic activities, journal issues, etc.\n\n
        <b>•</b> Event details for quarterly &amp; annual meetings with detailed Scientific Program\n\n
        <b>•</b> Journal of BNA, published at regular intervals\n\n
        <b>•</b> Interesting Cases that help users to learn and also participate with comments\n\n
        <b>•</b> Participate and win prizes in Quiz during events, through the Voting section\n\nFor any technical queries regarding the app, please contact <a href="mailto:digitalheatlh@cmplin.com">digitalheatlh@cmplin.com</a></string>
-->
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">
    <![CDATA[
        Bombay Neurosciences Association http://bombayneurosciences.org/ website, which provides the SERVICE of medical education to the neurology fraternity of medicinal practice.

        This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
        If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
        The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at, unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

        Information Collection and Use
        For a better experience while using our website and mobile app, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your
        name, phone number, and email address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.

        Log Data
        We want to inform you that whenever you visit our website and mobile app, we collect information that your browser sends to us, which is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.

        Cookies
        Cookies are files with small amounts of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive. Our website uses these “cookies” to collect information and to improve our Service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

        Service Providers
        We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:
        - To facilitate our Service
        - To provide the Service on our behalf
        - To perform Service-related services or
        - To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used

        We want to inform our Service users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.

        Security
        We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

        Links to Other Sites
        Our Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

        Children’s Privacy
        Our Services do not address anyone under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 18. In the case we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us
        with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.

        Changes to This Privacy Policy
        We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted
        on this page.

        Contact Us
        If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at: bombayneurosciences@gmail.com
        This Privacy Policy page was created at: http://bombayneurosciences.org/.
    ]]>

</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="about_bna_content">Bombay Neurosciences Association is a charitable trust registered under the Societies Act and formed for the purpose of bringing all medical specialties involved in the treatment and management of neurological patients under one roof   Aim of BNA is to foster interaction amongst all neurological specialties to stimulate learning and team building with the ultimate goal of improved patient care and outcome. The Executive Committee runs the day-to-day affairs of BNA and is elected annually.\n\nMain academic initiatives of BNA include quarterly and annual scientific meetings, journal publication, and case discussions on interesting cases.\n\nMost of the contribution for journals and cases comes from the members themselves.\n\nYou can contact BNA @ bombayneurosciences@gmail.com or 9869718979 / 9867618591</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Please wait..</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection">No Internet Connection</string>
</resources>